[upbeat music]
今天，让我们铭记
- Today, let us remember
那场摧毁了我们心爱咖啡馆的悲惨火灾
that the tragic fire that destroyed our beloved café
是一个绝佳的机会，让我们将其转变成更酷的地方
is an awesome opportunity to turn it into something cool
并提升我们的社交生活。
and upgrade our social lives.
我知道大家对于重建都有自己的想法
- I know we all have ideas about how to rebuild,
所以，让我们争论一下谁的主意最好
so let's fight over whose idea is best
然后决定采用我的方案。
and then decide to do mine.
请允许我展示——
May I present-- - Why do you get to go first?
为什么你先来？
- Simple. I own an easel.
简单。我有一个画架。
May I present--
我可以展示一下--
- So you brought that one from home?
所以你从家里带来了那个？
- This is my store easel. May I--
这是我店里的画架。我可以--
- Don't you have one at school?
你学校里没有吗？
- Okay, fine! I'm an easel guy.
好吧，好吧！我是画架的人。
So what?
那又怎样？
I'm also an idea guy.
我也是个有想法的人。
Presenting-- Ricky's Science of Sports Café.
展示一下--瑞奇的体育科学咖啡馆。
- Wow.
哇。
That was a waste of all your easels.
那真是浪费了你所有的画架。
Now,
现在，
envision a café
想象一个咖啡馆
where the tabletops look like soccer fields
那里的桌面看起来像足球场
and the waiters only serve food
而服务员只用脚上菜。
with their feet.
用脚？
- Ew! - Feet?
呃！
- Nasty.
恶心。
- I'm proposing a sports nutrition café
我提议的是一个运动营养咖啡馆
that features a carbo-loading buffet,
特色是碳水化合物加载自助餐，
a protein shake bar, and...
蛋白质奶昔吧，还有...
a cold-pressed juicery.
一个冷压果汁吧。
Please clap.
请鼓掌。
- They're holding their applause for my idea.
他们为我的想法鼓掌。
What we need is an extreme sports café
我们需要的是一个极限运动咖啡馆
with an extreme mini-ramp, extreme cheerleaders--
配备一个极限小型坡道，极限啦啦队——
- Couldn't you at least have taken the pizza out of the box?
你至少不能把披萨从盒子里拿出来吗？
- That's not just a pizza.
那不仅仅是一张披萨。
That's the floor.
那是地板。
This is gonna be the first café
这将是第一家咖啡馆
where you can not only eat off the floor--
你不仅可以从地板上吃——
you can eat the floor.
你可以吃地板。
Mmm. Delicious floor.
嗯，美味的地板。
So when do we start building?
我们什么时候开始建造？
- We're not building a pizza floor.
- 我们不是在建造披萨地板。
- Well, we're definitely not doing science.
- 好吧，我们肯定不是在做科学实验。
- Soccer is the world's most popular sport.
- 足球是世界上最受欢迎的运动。
- You can't do sports without nutrition.
- 没有营养你无法进行体育运动。
- Why do I even come to these meetings?
- 我为什么还要来参加这些会议？
They always end the same way.
它们总是以同样的方式结束。
- Okay, really? - You know what?
- 好吧，真的吗？ - 你知道吗？
Stay out of this meeting. - Come on, seriously?
别参加这个会议。 - 拜托，真的吗？
Okay, do you not think that this is a dumb idea?
好吧，你不觉得这是个愚蠢的主意吗？
[indistinct arguing]
[听不清的争吵]
- Kids. Kids!
- 孩子们。孩子们！
You can stop arguing.
你们可以停止争吵了。
Your dad and I have already decided
你爸爸和我已经决定了
what we're doing with the cafe.
我们怎么处理咖啡馆。
- Picture this.
- 想象一下。
The menacing feathers of a bird of prey.
猛禽的威胁性羽毛。
The razor's edge of steel blades.
钢刀的锋利边缘。
The shimmering majesty
闪耀的威严
of a skin-tight sequined body suit.
紧身亮片连体衣的华丽
- We're finally fulfilling our dream
- 我们终于要实现我们的梦想
and opening a café dedicated to the danger and elegance of...
并且开设一家专门致敬...的危险与优雅的咖啡馆
both: Ice dancing!
双方: 冰上舞蹈！
all: Ice dancing?
所有人: 冰上舞蹈？
both: Ice dancing!
双方: 冰上舞蹈！
- Normally, I don't like to get caught up
- 通常，我不喜欢被卷入
in your family nonsense,
你们家的那些荒唐事，
but I got to ask-- are you joking?
但我必须问——你在开玩笑吗？
Are you not joking?
你不是在开玩笑吧？
- The Dancing Harpers never joke.
- 舞者哈珀家的人从不开玩笑。
Anne?
安妮？
[Tchaikovsky's "Waltz of the Flowers" playing]
[柴可夫斯基的《花之圆舞曲》播放中]
- An ice dancing café?
- 一个冰舞咖啡馆？
None of our friends are gonna want to eat there.
我们的朋友都不会想去那里吃饭。
- We've been living with this shame our entire lives.
- 我们一生都在承受这种耻辱。
- They're taking the tragedy of a fire
- 他们把一场火灾的悲剧
and turning it into something bad.
变成了一件坏事。
- Ice dancing is lame.
- 冰舞很无聊。
- Super lame.
超级无聊。
- It's not even a sport.
这甚至不算是一项运动。
- I mean, how could something on ice
我的意思是，冰上的东西
be so uncool?
怎么会这么不酷？
- Come on, guys, maybe they'll find a way
拜托，伙计们，也许他们会找到办法
to make it cool.
让它变得酷起来。
- [yelling]
（大喊）
[crashing]
（撞击声）
- Or maybe not.
或者也许不会。
[upbeat music]
（欢快的音乐）
♪ ♪
[whistling]
吹口哨
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[upbeat music]
欢快的音乐
- Come on, Mom.
- 来吧，妈妈。
We have some really good ideas for this place.
我们为这个地方有一些非常好的想法。
- Honey, I'm sure your ideas are wonderful,
- 亲爱的，我相信你的想法很棒，
but this has been a dream of ours for a long, long time.
但这已经是我们长久以来的梦想了。
- Yep. We're gonna display our costumes, pictures, and trophies
是的。我们将展示我们的服装、照片和奖杯，
so we can share with the public
这样我们就可以与公众分享
the glory of the best days of our lives.
我们生命中最辉煌的时刻。
That is, up until the point you came into our lives.
也就是说，直到你进入我们的生活之前。
- If this has always been your dream, why'd you wait so long?
既然这是你们一直以来的梦想，为什么等了这么久？
- Well, there's always been one thing stopping us.
嗯，总有一个东西阻止我们。
- [snorts] Just one?
（嗤之以鼻）就一个？
- Yes, the most important piece of our history:
是的，我们历史中最重要的部分：
our missing practice skates.
我们丢失的训练冰鞋。
But we made a solemn promise that one day,
但我们曾郑重承诺，总有一天，
we'd find them and display them
我们会找到它们并展示它们
in our very own ice dancing wonderland.
在我们自己的冰舞仙境中。
- But this is Tom's Get Sporty.
- 但这不是汤姆的Get Sporty吗？
Shouldn't the new café be less sequiny and feathery
新咖啡馆不应该更少亮片和羽毛
and more, oh, I don't know,
而更多，哦，我不知道，
sporty?
运动风吗？
- What says "sporty" more than--
- 还有什么比——
both: Ice dancing?
两人齐声：冰舞更运动？
- Now we just need to head up to the mountains
- 现在我们只需要上山
and get our skates from the place we used to work.
从我们以前工作的地方拿回我们的冰鞋。
The old Check Please Roadhouse.
老查克请路屋。
- So let me get this straight.
- 让我搞清楚。
Once you get those skates,
一旦你拿到那些冰鞋，
this place turns into an ice dancing wonderland?
这个地方就会变成一个冰舞仙境？
- Yep. No skates, no glory.
- 是的。没有冰鞋，就没有荣耀。
- And we crave glory.
- 而我们渴望荣耀。
[both exclaiming]
[两人惊呼]
- Guys, we have got to get those skates before Mom and Dad do
- 伙计们，我们得在爸妈之前拿到那些冰鞋
and get rid of 'em.
并把它们处理掉。
No skates,
没有冰鞋，
no embarrassing ice dancing café.
没有让人尴尬的冰舞咖啡馆。
Easy peasy.
小菜一碟。
Mae, cover for us while we're gone.
梅，我们不在的时候帮我们打掩护。
- You know I can't lie to grown-ups.
你知道我不能对大人撒谎。
I always get nervous and do that weird laugh.
我总是会紧张，然后发出那种奇怪的笑声。
- Mae, do you know where the kids went?
梅，你知道孩子们去哪儿了吗？
- No.
不知道。
[giggles awkwardly]
[尴尬地笑]
- What's so funny?
有什么好笑的？
- Nothing.
没什么。
[giggling]
[咯咯笑]
I have to go to the bathroom.
我得去洗手间。
- Well, as soon as we find the kids,
嗯，一旦我们找到孩子们，
we can get on the road, huh? - Yeah.
我们就可以上路了，对吧？
Honey, I'm a little nervous
是的。
about going back to Check Please.
亲爱的，我对回到《请结账》有点紧张
- Oh, come on, honey. There's nothing to worry about.
哦，别担心，亲爱的。没什么好担心的。
Times have changed.
时代变了。
People are much more open-minded these days.
现在人们更加开放了。
Everybody accepts ice dancers.
大家都接受冰舞者了。
[indistinct chatter]
- All right.
好吧。
We get the skates and then get home
我们拿到冰鞋，然后赶在
before Mom and Dad even know we're gone.
爸妈发现我们不在之前回家。
Easy peasy.
小菜一碟。
Oh, uh, excuse me.
哦，呃，打扰一下。
We're looking for some information
我们在找一些关于
about some people who used to work here.
曾经在这里工作过的人的信息。
Tom and Anne. They were ice dancers.
汤姆和安妮。他们是花样滑冰选手。
[all gasping]
（所有人惊讶）
- Did you say "ice dancers"?
- 你是说“冰舞者”吗？
'Cause this here's a hockey hangout.
因为这里是个冰球聚集地。
We don't like dirty ice dancers.
我们不喜欢脏兮兮的冰舞者。
- Oh, come on. Settle down, Zach Le'Ben.
- 哦，得了吧。冷静点，Zach Le'Ben。
They didn't say they liked ice dancers.
他们没说他们喜欢冰舞者。
In fact, it looks like they got a beef with them.
事实上，看起来他们和冰舞者有矛盾。
You guys got a beef with them, right?
你们和冰舞者有矛盾，对吧？
- Yep. - Beef.
- 是的。 - 有矛盾。
- Big beef. - Yeah.
- 很大的矛盾。 - 是的。
- Lots of meat.
- 很多矛盾。
- I like beef. I miss it.
- 我喜欢牛肉。我想念它。
- Oh!
- 哦！
- You know, I might remember Tom and Anne.
- 你知道，我可能记得汤姆和安妮。
- Wait, what do you mean, "might"?
- 等等，你说的“可能”是什么意思？
- Well, the more you order, the mightier my memory gets.
- 嗯，你点的越多，我的记忆就越强大。
- Fine.
- 好吧。
We'll share some extra-hot Detroit Red Wings.
我们来点超辣的底特律红翼队。
- I'm remembering Tom.
- 我在记起汤姆。
- And a couple of Calgary flame-broiled burgers.
- 还有几个卡尔加里火焰烤汉堡。
- Ah, yes, Tom and Anne.
- 啊，是的，汤姆和安妮。
I'll put your order in.
我会把你的订单录入。
- We said "easy peasy."
- 我们说的是'轻而易举'。
But now I'm shaking in my kneesies.
但现在我膝盖都在发抖。
[upbeat music] - ♪ Oh oh oh ♪
[欢快音乐]
[upbeat music]
♪ 哦 哦 哦 ♪
[whistling]
[欢快音乐]
- Now, where were we?
[吹口哨]
- Well, we were right here,
- 那么，我们说到哪儿了？
and you were right...
- 嗯，我们就在这儿，
there.
而你就在那儿。
- Oh, right. Tom and Anne.
哦，对了。汤姆和安妮。
Now, they weren't like the others who hung out here.
现在，他们不像那些经常在这里闲逛的人。
They were ice dancers.
他们是花样滑冰选手。
Skating under the radar in a world ruled by the Mullets.
在一个被‘鲻鱼头’统治的世界里，他们低调地滑冰。
- Wait, what's a mullet?
等等，什么是‘鲻鱼头’？
- Not what. Who.
不是‘什么’，而是‘谁’。
Hanson, Branson, Danson, and Smith,
汉森、布兰森、丹森和史密斯，
four mean and nasty hockey players
四个以鲻鱼头发型著称的凶狠冰球运动员。
known for their mullet hairstyle.
前面是正经，后面是派对。
Business in the front and par-tay in the back.
这里没有正经，只有派对！
- No business here. Just par-tay!
- 这里没有正经事，只有派对！
- Anyway, the Mullets thought ice dancing was lame.
- 总之，那些‘鲻鱼头’们觉得冰舞很逊。
- It's not lame. It's super lame.
- 不是逊，是非常逊。
- It's not even a sport.
- 这根本不算运动。
- You sound like the Mullets.
- 你听起来就像那些‘鲻鱼头’。
In fact, you four kind of look like they did back in the day.
实际上，你们四个看起来有点像他们当年的样子。
Let me take you back to that day.
让我带你们回到那一天。
It was the 1990s.
那是20世纪90年代。
Just like today, except phones weren't smart,
就像今天，只是手机没那么智能，
but people still were.
但人们依然聪明。
[rock music]
- Yeah! - Mullets in the house!
- 是的！ - 这里有人留着鲻鱼头！
[all cheering]
- Can I get my check please?
- 可以给我结账吗？
- I'll give you a hockey check.
- 我来给你一个冰球式的检查。
Ha-ha!
哈哈！
- [grunts]
- [咕哝声]
- What is this?
- 这是什么？
- Hey!
- 嘿！
Why is our table dirty?
- 为什么我们的桌子这么脏？
- Ah, hockey sticks. Waitress!
- 啊，曲棍球杆。服务员！
- Sorry, I'll take care of it right away.
- 对不起，我马上处理。
Ooh. Hi.
哦。嗨。
- Tables in here used to be clean.
- 这里的桌子以前都是干净的。
- I can't stand a dirty table!
- 我无法忍受脏桌子！
- Only thing worse than a dirty table
- 比脏桌子更糟糕的
is a dirty ice dancer!
- 是脏的冰舞者！
[laughter]
[笑声]
You haven't seen any, have you?
你没见过任何，对吧？
- Oh, no, believe me.
- 哦，不，相信我。
You Mullets would be the first to know
你们这群红发人要是看到冰舞选手了，肯定会第一个知道
if I saw any ice dancers.
脏兮兮的！
- Dirty!
冰舞选手
Ice dancers.
对
- Right.
脏兮兮，脏兮兮的冰舞选手
- Dirty, dirty ice dancers.
听到了吗？她多加了一个'脏'
- Hear that? She threw in an extra "dirty."
她挺不错的
She's all right.
所有人：是啊！
all: Yeah!
那些脏兮兮的冰舞选手最好识相点，别在这附近露面
- Guess those dirty ice dancers know better
嗯，如果他们真来了...
than to show their dirty ice-dancing faces around here.
那些脏兮兮的冰舞者知道最好不要在这里露面。
- Well, if they ever do,
好吧，如果他们真的来了，
we're gonna open up a big can of Mullet justice!
我们就会打开一大罐鲻鱼正义！
all: Yeah!
大家：没错！
- Mullet justice. Your table's ready.
鲻鱼正义。你的桌子准备好了。
- Tom? - What?
汤姆？
- What if those mullets find out we're ice dancers?
如果那些鲻鱼发现我们是冰舞者怎么办？
They'll turn everyone in this place against us.
他们会煽动这里的每个人反对我们。
We'll lose our jobs. You'll probably lose some teeth.
我们会丢掉工作。你可能还会掉几颗牙。
[both gasp]
[两人同时倒吸一口凉气]
The nationals are on TV. You need your pearly whites.
全国锦标赛在电视上播出。你需要你的珍珠白牙齿。
- I do have beautiful teeth.
- 我确实有一口漂亮的牙齿。
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
- I don't care what those Mullets think.
- 我不在乎那些鲻鱼头怎么想。
We will not skate in the shadows anymore.
我们不会再在阴影中滑冰了。
I am a winner. - [gasps]
我是个赢家。
Oh, Tom, your foolishness is only outdone by your talent.
哦，汤姆，你的愚蠢只有你的才华能超越。
- I swear on our practice skates,
- 我以我们的练习冰鞋发誓，
someday we're gonna break free of this place
总有一天我们会摆脱这个地方
and open our own ice dancing café.
然后开我们自己的冰舞咖啡馆。
[exclaims]
[惊呼]
Because this should never have to hide.
因为这本不应该被隐藏。
- [gasps]
[喘气]
- Just like me, the patty stuck the landing.
就像我一样，肉饼完美着陆。
Order up!
订单好了！
- Wow.
哇。
They were so brave.
他们真勇敢。
- Brave? They were playing with fire.
勇敢？他们是在玩火。
- And the whole time, no one knew they were
而整个过程中，没人知道他们是
"you-know-what's"?
“你知道的什么”？
- Ice dancers.
- 冰舞者。
- [laughs nervously] Are lame!
- [紧张地笑] 真逊！
Grr!
Grr！
- Yes, they were playing with fire.
- 是的，他们在玩火。
But when you play with fire too long, you get burned.
但当你玩火玩得太久，你就会被烧伤。
- Ice dancers!
- 冰舞者！
both: Aah! - We don't want any trouble!
两人: 啊！ - 我们不想惹麻烦！
- We just want to be free to skate our way too.
- 我们只是想自由地滑我们的方式。
I mean, isn't there enough room on the ice for everybody?
我的意思是，冰上难道没有足够的空间给每个人吗？
- No! Hockey rules. Ice dancers drool.
- 不！冰球至上。冰舞者逊毙了。
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
- We don't tolerate ice dancers in here.
- 我们这里不接受花样滑冰的。
- My daddy never did.
- 我爸爸从没接受过。
His daddy never did.
他爸爸也从没接受过。
His daddy's mama did,
他爸爸的妈妈倒是接受过，
but she was a progressive woman.
但她是个开明的女人。
Anyway, it's just the way it's always been!
反正，一直都是这样！
- You know what?
- 你知道吗？
We should build a wall around this place
我们应该在这地方周围建一堵墙
to keep you ice dancers out!
把你们这些花样滑冰的挡在外面！
- We don't have the money for that.
- 我们没有那么多钱来做这个。
- Doesn't matter.
- 没关系。
We'll make the ice dancers
我们会让那些滑冰的人
pay for it.
来付这笔钱。
- Yeah!
- 对！
all: Mullets! Mullets! Mullets!
所有人: 鲻鱼头！鲻鱼头！鲻鱼头！
- Can't we all just skate along?
- 我们不能一起滑冰吗？
- The wall just got 10 feet taller!
- 墙刚刚又高了十英尺！
- Boom!
- 砰！
all: Mullets! Mullets! Mullets!
所有人: 鲻鱼头！鲻鱼头！鲻鱼头！
- You better run. You don't want
你最好快跑，你不会想遇到那个鲻鱼头正义的。
any of that Mullet justice.
你为什么帮我们？- 因为我曾经也年轻过，恋爱过，也有过冰上舞蹈的梦想。
- Why are you helping us? - Because I was once young
哦！
and in love and had dreams of ice dancing too.
嘿！
- Oh!
快走！滚开！
- [grunts]
哇，哇，哇，所以他们就这样跑了？
- Go on! Get!
如果你让我说完-
[both exclaiming]
那他们的梦想呢
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, so they just ran out of there?
赢得全国冠军呢？- 我能说完吗？
- If you let me finish-- - What about their dreams
你恋爱过？- 我还有其他客人。
of winning the nationals? - Can I just finish?
赢得全国冠军的梦想呢？ - 我能说完吗？
- You were in love? - I have other customers.
- 你恋爱了？ - 我还有其他客户。
- Who paid for the wall? - I'm just gonna finish.
- 谁付的钱建墙？ - 我只想说完。
Tom and Anne were able to duck under a table and hide...
汤姆和安妮能够躲在桌子下面...
[all chanting "Mullets!"]
[所有人齐声高喊“鲻鱼头！”]
- Tom, the only way to calm that angry mob
- 汤姆，平息那群愤怒人群的唯一办法
is to stand up to those Mullets.
就是勇敢面对那些鲻鱼头。
I mean, they're just kids.
我的意思是，他们只是孩子。
- There's four of them, Anne,
- 他们有四个人，安妮，
and they're crazy!
而且他们很疯狂！
Just promise me if we ever have kids,
只要答应我，如果我们将来有孩子，
we won't have four.
我们不会要四个。
- Ugh, promise.
- 呃，我答应。
- Where'd they go?
- 他们去哪儿了？
- Just in case we don't make it out of here,
- 以防我们无法离开这里，
there's something I want everybody to know,
有些事情我想让大家知道，
or at least anybody who climbs under this table.
至少是任何爬到这张桌子下面的人。
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
- [exclaims]
- [惊呼]
- Well, what do we got here?
- 那么，我们这里有什么？
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- "Tom loves Anne"?
- '汤姆爱安妮'?
- [gasps]
- [吸气声]
You do? - [chuckles]
你真的？ - [轻笑]
- I love-- - Knock it off!
- 我爱—— - 别闹了！
This is a hockey hangout.
这里是冰球聚集地。
There's no love.
没有爱情的。
- Yeah. We may hug after a goal,
- 是的。我们可能在进球后拥抱，
but there's no love.
但那不是爱情。
- Now, are you gonna get up and leave
- 现在，你是自己站起来离开
on your own?
自己走吗？
- Or are we gonna have to
- 还是我们要
check you outta here?
把你赶出去？
- We're going!
- 我们走！
- Oh, no. You go.
- 哦，不。你走。
The skates stay.
冰鞋留下。
- Now scram, Brace Face.
- 现在滚，牙套脸。
- But-- - He said "Scram, Brace Face."
- 但是—— - 他说了“滚，牙套脸。”
Come on. - Okay.
来吧。 - 好的。
I just, um-- I left the stove on.
我只是，嗯——我忘了关炉子。
all: Get out!
全体: 出去!
- And we never want to see your kind in here again!
- 我们再也不想在这里看到你们这种人了!
Ha!
哈!
all: Mullets! Mullets!
全体: 鲻鱼头! 鲻鱼头!
♪ ♪
- Remember, they never wanted "to see our kind
- 记得吗,他们说过'再也不想在那里看到我们这种人'吗?
in there again"?
所以我们就以他们的身份进去。
So we'll just go in there
- 我戴着这头盔什么也看不见,
as their kind.
但伪装成他们去《请结账》也许能行。
- I can't see anything under this helmet,
- 没错,我们就这么大摇大摆地进去,
but going undercover to Check Please just might work.
但伪装成“Check Please”的顾客或许能行得通。
- Yep, we'll just waltz in,
没错，我们就这么大摇大摆地进去，
grab the skates, and waltz out.
拿了溜冰鞋，再大摇大摆地出来。
- Waltz, Tom?
华尔兹，汤姆？
- Oh, dang it, Anne.
哦，该死，安妮。
I just can't hide my true nature.
我就是无法隐藏我的本性。
- Mae, are you hiding?
梅，你在躲藏吗？
- No.
没有。
[giggling awkwardly]
[尴尬地笑]
- Okay, well, we're about to get on the road.
好吧，我们马上就要上路了。
Do you know where the kids are?
你知道孩子们在哪里吗？
- No.
不知道。
[giggling awkwardly]
（尴尬地笑）
Okay, fine.
好吧，好吧。
Here's the truth.
这是真相。
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la ♪
啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦
- ♪ Hey ♪ - ♪ La, la, la, la ♪
嘿 啦，啦，啦，啦
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
啦，啦，啦，啦，啦
- Wow, I can't believe
哇，我简直不敢相信
how mean those Mullets were to Mom and Dad.
那些Mullets对爸爸妈妈那么刻薄。
- I can't believe I ate all those wings
我不敢相信我吃了那么多鸡翅
and a burger.
还有汉堡。
Mm.
嗯。
[groans]
[呻吟]
But what about the skates?
那滑冰鞋呢？
What happened to the skates?
滑冰鞋怎么了？
- Oh, I don't want any trouble.
哦，我不想惹麻烦。
If you really must know,
如果你真的必须知道，
ask them.
去问他们。
- Mullets in the house! - [laughs]
鲻鱼头们来了！ - [笑]
[half-hearted cheers]
[有气无力的欢呼]
[laughs]
[笑声]
[both grunt]
[两人同时发出咕哝声]
- Wow, that hair really is a party in the back.
- 哇，那头发后脑勺真是个派对。
- They don't look so mean.
- 他们看起来并不凶。
Maybe they've changed.
也许他们已经改变了。
- Our table's dirty!
- 我们的桌子脏了！
[laughs evilly]
[邪恶地笑]
- Or maybe they stayed the same.
- 或者他们还是老样子。
- Nothing worse than a dirty table.
- 没有什么比脏桌子更糟糕的了。
- Except dirty ice dancers.
- 除了脏兮兮的冰舞者。
- Yeah. [both laugh]
- 是啊。[两人笑]
- Ooh, guess we'll grab some waiting wings.
- 哦，看来我们得拿些等待的翅膀。
[all laugh] - Pfft.
[大家都笑] - 噗。
Ice dancing. Lame.
冰舞。无聊。
- Super lame.
- 超级无聊。
- Not even a sport!
- 甚至不算运动！
- How can something that's done on the ice be so uncool?
- 怎么能在冰上做的事情这么不酷？
- Whoa. They sound just like us.
- 哇。他们听起来就像我们。
- We never said that.
- 我们从来没说过那样的话。
- We said exactly that. About Mom and Dad.
我们确实说过。关于妈妈和爸爸。
- Well, not in a mean way.
嗯，不是以一种刻薄的方式。
- What other way is there?
还有其他方式吗？
- Look, I hate to say this, guys, but...
听着，我不想这么说，伙计们，但是...
we're exactly like those Mullets.
我们和那些鱼尾辫一模一样。
- I don't see it.
我没看出来。
- Maybe we should forget about the skates.
也许我们应该忘记溜冰鞋。
- No.
不。
We're still getting the skates,
我们还是要买溜冰鞋，
but not to keep them from Mom and Dad.
但不是为了阻止妈妈和爸爸。
To give them to Mom and Dad.
给妈妈和爸爸。
They had a dream,
他们有一个梦想，
and we're gonna make that dream come true.
我们要让那个梦想成真。
- Yeah. - Let's do it.
- 是的。 - 我们做吧。
- It burns! - Wipe it off.
- 好烫！ - 擦掉它。
- But I'm not done. Mmm. Mmm.
- 但我还没吃完。嗯。嗯。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- These L.A. Kings crabs are great.
- 这些洛杉矶国王队的螃蟹真棒。
I love food that comes with a hammer.
我喜欢带锤子的食物。
[all laugh and grunt]
[所有人都笑和咕哝]
- Wow, I cannot believe it.
哇，我简直不敢相信。
You guys are the famous Mullets!
你们就是著名的鲻鱼头乐队！
- Is it true you guys once ran
听说你们曾经把一对不干净的冰舞组合赶出这里？
a dirty ice-dancing duo out of here?
抱歉，你得说得再具体点。
- Sorry, you're gonna have to be more specific.
是啊，因为我们赶走了无数不干净的冰舞组合。
- Yeah, 'cause we've run countless
大家都笑了
dirty ice-dancing duos outta here.
这两个人在这里工作过，
[all laugh]
而且——我简直不敢相信这有多棒——
- Well, these two worked here
但据说，你们偷了他们的冰鞋？
and--I can't believe how awesome this is--
哦，是的。
but supposedly, you stole their skates?
但据说，你偷了他们的冰鞋？
all: Oh yeah.
所有人: 哦，是的。
- That must have been beautiful.
- 那一定很美妙。
- It wasn't terrible,
- 并不糟糕，
and don't touch me.
而且别碰我。
- So what did you guys do with those skates?
- 那你们用那些冰鞋做了什么？
- We put them in the perfect spot
- 我们把它们放在了一个完美的位置
to remind ice dancers of their place in the world.
来提醒冰舞者他们在世界上的位置。
- [laughs evilly] - Yup, for the last 20-odd years
- [邪恶地笑] - 是的，过去20多年里
they've been in the men's room
它们一直在男厕所里
holding the toilet paper!
拿着卫生纸！
[all laugh]
[大家都笑了]
- Hey, we should go check out those skates!
- 嘿，我们应该去看看那些冰鞋！
- Let's do it. - Yeah.
- 走吧。 - 好。
- Good, 'cause those Detroit Red Wings
- 好，因为那些底特律红翼队
and that Calgary Flame-broiled burger
和那个卡尔加里火焰烤肉汉堡
are headed for a shoot out,
正准备进行一场对决，
if you know what I mean.
如果你明白我的意思。
[all laugh]
[大家都笑了]
- Oh, I get it, man.
- 哦，我明白了，伙计。
- What does he mean?
他什么意思？
both: I don't know.
不知道。
- All right, let's get out of here.
好吧，我们离开这里。
Wait, why didn't you take the paper off?
等等，你为什么不把纸拿掉？
- We have no idea how they got it on!
我们根本不知道他们是怎么贴上去的！
- Let's just go.
我们走吧。
- Nice meeting you guys!
很高兴见到你们！
all: Dicky! - Nice meeting you, too.
迪基！也很高兴见到你。
Hey, what are you doing with our toilet skates?
嘿，你拿我们的厕所滑板做什么？
- Run! - Hey!
跑！嘿！
- Somebody stop those brats!
有人快去拦住那些捣蛋鬼！
- Get outta there! - Oh, here we go again.
快出来！- 哎，又来了。
- Hey, check it out.
嘿，看看这个。
"Tom loves Anne." This is their table!
“汤姆爱安妮。”这是他们的桌子！
- You've got till the count of three.
你们还有三秒钟。
One! - What are we gonna do?
一！- 我们该怎么办？
- We're gonna use the thing they hate most against them.
我们要用他们最讨厌的东西来对付他们。
- Three!
三！
- All right, hand 'em over.
好吧，把它们交出来。
- No.
不。
These skates aren't yours.
这些滑冰鞋不是你的。
They belong to our mom and dad.
它们属于我们的妈妈和爸爸。
You may remember them as the waitress and Brace Face.
你可能记得他们是那个女服务员和牙套脸。
The dirty ice dancers. - [gasps]
那对肮脏的冰舞者。 - [吸气声]
That makes you the spawn of dirty ice dancers.
那意味着你是肮脏冰舞者的后代。
- And proud of it. - [gasps]
- 并且以此为荣。 - [吸气声]
Ice dancing is one of the most hard-core sports there is.
冰舞是现有最硬核的运动之一。
[all laugh]
[大家都笑]
You think you gotta be tough to play hockey?
你以为打冰球需要很强硬吗？
Check this out.
看看这个。
[Tchaikovsky's "Waltz of the Flowers"]
[柴可夫斯基的《花之圆舞曲》]
[both scoff] - Nicky...
[两人嗤之以鼻] - 尼基...
♪ ♪
- Ooh, look.
- 哦，看。
They're gonna impress us with your fancy spins?
他们要用你那华丽的旋转来打动我们吗？
[grunts] - Whoa!
[咕哝] - 哇！
- Dude, you just got decked by a kid!
- 伙计，你刚被一个小孩打倒了！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- Whoa.
- 哇。
You guys are pathetic.
你们真是可悲。
♪ ♪
[grunts]
（咕哝声）
♪ ♪
- Looks like you're all out of brothers.
看来你的兄弟们都出局了。
This is gonna be fun.
这会很有趣的。
- Yes, yes, it is.
是的，是的，确实如此。
- I need you guys to settle down here.
我需要你们在这里冷静下来。
- Aw, hockey sticks.
哦，冰球棍。
[grunts]
（咕哝声）
♪ ♪
Okay, let's get outta here!
好的，我们离开这里吧！
- There any dirty ice dancers in here?
- 这里有脏兮兮的冰舞者吗？
- There better not be! Or we'll check 'em
- 最好没有！否则我们会把他们
right out the door!
直接赶出门！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
all: [distorted voice] Wait!
全体：[扭曲的声音] 等等！
[all gasp]
[全体吸气]
- I told 'em twenty years ago
- 我二十年前就告诉他们
to turn that stove off!
要把炉子关掉！
- [sighs] What're we gonna do now?
- [叹气] 我们现在该怎么办？
- Well, it's not your skates,
好吧，这不是你的冰鞋，
but hopefully it'll do.
但希望它能派上用场。
- You know what? This table is even better.
你知道吗？这张桌子甚至更好。
- You're mom's right, and the fact that
你妈妈说得对，而且你用冰舞动作对付那些家伙
you used ice dancing moves against The Mullets
让这一切更加完美。
makes it even sweeter. [all chuckle]
Dawn刚刚像扔布娃娃一样把我们扔出去了。
- Dawn just chucked us like rag dolls.
我是说，我还能说什么呢？
- I mean, what can I say?
我有妈妈的力气。
I've got mom's strength.
还有你爸爸的美貌。
- And your father's beauty. - [laughs]
你知道，也许你天生就是个冰舞者。
You know, maybe you were born to be an ice dancer.
- Maybe I was, and that wouldn't be that bad.
也许我是，那也不坏。
- Oh, and thanks for using our ideas in the new café.
哦，还有，谢谢你在新咖啡馆里用了我们的点子。
- Yeah, now we've got a café... - Oh!
是啊，现在我们有了一个咖啡馆...
- That includes everybody.
那是包容所有人的。
- Yeah. - all: Three, two, one!
对。
- Come on in, everybody.
大家快进来。
[cheers and applause]
欢呼和掌声
[gasps] - Oh!
吸气声
Maia Shibutani?
Maia Shibutani？
- Alex Shibutani?
- 亚历克斯·涩谷？
- Anne Harper? - Tom Harper?
- 安妮·哈珀？ - 汤姆·哈珀？
- The Shib Sibs!
- 涩谷兄妹！
- The Harp...ers.
- 哈珀...们。
- You guys are ice dancing champions!
- 你们是冰舞冠军！
- Whoa, whoa, you know our parents?
- 哇，哇，你们认识我们的父母？
- Know them? They're legends.
- 认识？他们是传奇。
- And we wanted to check out their new café.
- 我们想来看看他们的新咖啡馆。
- Let me ask you.
- 让我问你。
Would you eat a floor if it were made of pizza?
如果地板是用披萨做的，你会吃吗？
- Heck yeah! In fact, I've always dreamed
当然愿意！实际上，我一直梦想着在披萨上滑冰。
of ice dancing on pizza.
这家伙懂我。
- This guy gets it.
看吧？我就说吧。
- See? I told you.
冰舞者也可以很酷。
Ice dancers can be cool.
嘿，我们可以展示一些我们的动作吗？
- Hey, can we show you some of our moves?
也许你可以在下次的表演中用到。
Maybe you can use them in your next routine.
好的。
- Yeah. - Oh.
哦。
Nicky.
尼基。
- [grunts and thuds]
（咕哝和撞击声）
- My easels!
我的画架！
- Everyone thinks it's so easy.
每个人都觉得这很容易。
- Why does he have three easels?
他为什么有三个画架？
- Like I said,
就像我说的，
this guy gets it.
这家伙懂的。
- Still got it.
依旧在行。
♪♪
- ♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
[whistling]
♪ [口哨声] ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪